[](https://www.byutv.org/)  Privacy Policy[](https://www.byutv.org/search)

Privacy Policy
==============

Thank you for visiting our Web site! We strive to make our Web presence a secure, private, and reliable place. This Privacy Statement explains how we collect and use information. This Privacy Statement only applies to our Web site, and not to any other sites, including sites for which we may offer hyperlinks from our site.

What information do you collect?
--------------------------------

When you sign up for a BYUtv account, service, or promotion, we ask you to register using personal information like your name, e-mail address, and account password. You may also choose to provide personal information in connection with comment forms, pledge or membership submissions, subscription registration, or purchases from our Web site.

BYUtv's servers also automatically record information that your browser sends when you visit our Web site or use some of our products. Our server logs record information like your Web request, Internet protocol address, browser type and language, cookies that uniquely indentify your browser, and the date and time of your request.

You are welcome to [contact](https://www.byutv.org/contact) BYUtv at any time to ask for your personal information to be changed, edited, or removed.

How do you use my personal information?
---------------------------------------

We use your personal information to provide the services you request and for internal purposes. For example, we may combine personal information we collect from you with information from other BYUtv services or third parties to enhance your user experience by customizing content for you. We also use your personal information to improve the quality of our services and technology as well as for our marketing, auditing, research, and analysis purposes.

When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with this Privacy Statement. We may also require additional confidentiality and security measures from them as an additional protective measure.

BYUtv never sells your personal information to third parties. We may, however, disclose aggregated, non-personal information with third parties. We may also disclose personal information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when you provide your consent to that disclosure, when we are required or permitted to do so by regulation, law, or government request, when we take actions to prevent fraud or imminent harm, and when we protect against harm to the rights, property and safety of BYUtv, its users, and the public.

Is my personal information secure?
----------------------------------

BYUtv uses encryption technology for transmitting information via your Internet browser. To ensure full use of this technology, we suggest you upgrade your browser and device software to the latest version available. A secured page can be identified by looking at the URL in your address bar. If it says "https://" instead of "http://" you are using a secured page to transmit your information to us.

We restrict access to personal information to BYUtv employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our services. We also take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of our data, including any personal information of yours that we store.

What about cookies?
-------------------

When you visit a BYUtv web site, we send cookies—small files containing a string of characters—to your computer that uniquely identify your browser. A cookie stored on your computer can be used to "remember" things like your password, or that you have already registered. We use cookies to improve the quality of our services, to store user preferences, to track user trends (such as how people browse our web sites), and to compile statistical data.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you prefer not to accept cookies, disabling cookies will not prevent you from visiting any portion of our Web site. However, some of our features or services may not function properly as a result.

What about internet protocol addresses?
---------------------------------------

An Internet protocol address, or IP address, is the unique number assigned to your computer or device by your Internet service provider. IP addresses do not identify you exclusively. We log IP addresses for use in our own internal statistical evaluation of the traffic on our Web site and to help us provide a better Web experience for our users.

What about links to other Web sites?
------------------------------------

You should be aware that our Web sites offer links to other, third-party Web sites that are not affiliated with BYUtv. When you link to other Web sites from ours, please be aware that these Web sites are beyond our control, and they may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, or solicit personal information from you. We recommend that you read the privacy policy of any Web site you are visiting.

We offer some of our services in connection with other Web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to BYUtv in order to deliver your requested service. We process your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Statement, but the other Web sites may operate under different privacy practices from ours.

Information for Security for Emloyees and Contractors
-----------------------------------------------------

We carefully train and supervise all employees who deal with credit card transactions. Credit card information is never written down except in extreme cases, after which the information is immediately shredded.

Return/Refund Policy
--------------------

BYUtv will refund a transaction within 90 days of the original transaction date. If a gift is received in return for the donation, the gift must be returned to BYUB before the 90 day limit and refunds will not be issued until gift is returned.

What if I have a question or complaint?
---------------------------------------

We make good-faith business efforts to provide you with access to your personal information upon request and to correct inaccurate data or delete your personal information. When you send e-mail or other communication to BYUtv, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our services.

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Statement at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of this Web site following the posting of any changes means that you have accepted and agree to those changes.

If you have any questions, comments, or criticisms regarding this Privacy Statement or BYUtv's information practices please contact us! You can view our [contact](https://www.byutv.org/contact) information on the contact page.

Leave Feedback

### watch together

The mission of BYUtv is to create purposeful, engaging viewing and listening experiences that entertain, inspire, uplift, and improve families and communities. Our vision is to be the family entertainment brand that young people want, parents trust, and families enjoy together.

© 2024 BYU Broadcasting. All rights reserved.

A Service of Brigham Young University.

Client Version: 5.0.5212

API Version: 5.62.0

Our live channel is free, but you need  
to be signed in to view some content.

Preview has Ended

Create Free Account / Sign In

Play

0:00

0:00

\-0:00

Speed

CC Settings

More

More

Captions On

Share

Start Over

Skip Back

Play

Skip Fwd

Up Next

Volume

Minimize

Fullscreen

### Caption Settings

Size

* Small
* Normal
* Large

Quick-Styles

* Style 1
* Style 2
* Style 3
* Style 4
* Style 5
* Style 6

Language

### Advanced Caption Settings

### Advanced Caption Settings

Font

Aa

Aa

Aa

50%

75%

100%

Background/Highlight

0%

50%

100%

Caption Window

0%

50%

100%

### Share

Share Full Show 

Create and Share Clip 

### Speed

0.75x

Normal

1.25x

1.5x

1.75x

2x

### Quality

Good

Better

Best

Higher Bandwidth

Lower Bandwidth
